(Howard:)How did Penny meet an astronaut?
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
(Bernadette:)The regular way
people meet astronauts.
(Howard:)Most of those
guys live in Texas.
(Bernadette:)Obviously, this one doesn't.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Bernadette:)Leonard lives here.
Priya's from India.
(Bernadette:)People meet, Howard.
God!
(Penny:)Fine.
(Bernadette:)You've met lots of astronauts,
(Bernadette:)and I've never grilled you
about that.
(Bernadette:)I'd thank you to extend me
the same courtesy.
I'm not grilling you;
I was just curious.
(Leonard:)I still can't get over the fact
that she got a big movie part.
(Leonard:)Not that I care what my ex-girlfriend's
up to, 'cause I don't.
(Bernadette:)Maybe that's where she met
the astronaut, all right?
(Priya:)I'm sorry. What would an
astronaut be doing
(Priya:)working on a movie?
(Bernadette:)He's a consultant.
(Leonard:)I thought the movie was
about 18th-century Vienna.
He can't have a hobby?!